rose-gardening-made-easy.com 2012-10-04

# Privacy Policy, About Your Private Information

## Privacy Policy Information For  
Rose Gardening Made Easy

It's important that you read Rose Gardening Made Easy's Privacy Policy information, before using this web site. 

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use www.rose-gardening-made-easy.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

www.rose-gardening-made-easy.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website. 

**Personal Information**

www.rose-gardening-made-easy.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number. 

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries. 

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties. 

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables www.rose-gardening-made-easy.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site. 

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site. 

We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site. 

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose. 

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cockie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with my site should you so choose. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

**Non-Personal Information**

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

**Release of Information**

If www.rose-gardening-made-easy.com is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us. 

**How You Can Correct or Remove Information**

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on this link and/or use our Contact Us page. 

**Updates and Effective Date** www.rose-gardening-made-easy.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

ADDRESS Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our website. 

KIDS AND PARENTS 

Although there is not - nor ever will be - anything intentionally offensive on my website, it is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases or asking questions on this site. 

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so. If you're worried about your children's activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator thru our "Contact Me" page.If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail me at my "Contact Me" section of the website.. I welcome your questions and feedback. 

Additional Note: Google Adsense 

If you elect to click on an ad generated by Google AdSense, make note of their policies as follows: 

Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies 

What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? 

The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. 

Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie: 

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative, or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information: 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here. 

You can find additional information in Appendix A of the NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers (PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time. 

For more information, you can read Google's policy on Adsense here: 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, ****

###  **[Click Here ****](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)**

 ** **

**Agreeing to Terms**

If you do not agree to rose-gardening-made-easy.com Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. 

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy. 

****
